Here onwards we started an exercise on
transformation readiness for EMEA sites,
mostly Helsingborg, Val De Reuil,
Sezanne and Wuppertal.
For these four sites,
we conduct a Phase zero assessment to
really understand the business complexity,
the capability of the site to adopt the
oneS4 template as being designed in
Pomezia, Mandra,
and the US as well as to identify any
specific unique challenges at the site
that that we wanted to document.
So we got a great deal of information
from the site mostly on the As-Is to
really understand
the complexity of the manufacturing
process at these sites as well as whether
or not,
what stage of maturity they are in and
what would it take for them to adopt the
OneS4 template,
that was our original ask from conducting
the Phase zero assessment.
And we have a very detailed report.
I believe most of you might have seen it.
If you have not seen, do let us know.
We'll share the report out to you guys to
take a look.
Out of that report came very good detail
in terms of unique capabilities that
these sites have.
And we wanted to deep dive further more
into those sites to ensure that OneS4
Template road map and the plan for
deployment can be built and how much
enhancement customizations configurations
that are needed.
We wanted to document ahead of the
release itself.
Release tentatively is marked to start
sometime end of this year,
mostly beginning of next year,
after Pomezia's go-live and hyper care.
So.
So given that we have some time to
prepare,
wish to deep dive into the major
challenges that we have identified.
There are approximately 28
major gaps that are requested by these
sites. Out of those,
we are looking into a few of them to
which will give us 80 to 90% of the
impact on the changes that are required
and then we wish to see what additional
details that we can collect and
information that we can collect which
will help us.
to prepare a build a plan for one is for
deployment. So.
So given that any questions before we
deep dive into the ask itself.
Nope.
So yeah, Hamza, let's start then.
Right. So just a few other things, right.
So these are the big rocks that we're
going to look at right for the first two
months,
we will concentrate on the Helsingborg
site, on the finance process,
royalty lease,
which is this session today.
At the same time, in two weeks time,
we will,
once the French teams in Val-de-Reuil are
back, we will start with the Toll,
Non-toll operations on one same physical
plant. I think that's a big,
big rock from the Val-de-Reuil side of
things.
And then once September hits around,
we will be able to concentrate on the
more manufacturing side of big rocks,
including the supermarket physical setup
and the Kanban,
as well as the Pas X integration across
the Helsingborg sites.
At the same time, for Val de Reuil,
which has a few more big rocksmto address,
we want to, once we address the toll,
non-toll situation and that should roll
over to the material identifier for
Pharma consumer goods.
As well as helping with the purchase of
raw materials of J&J, Belgium,
also the QA release of EU Imports,
which is a big factor as part of Val de
Reuil site as well as finishing off with
The GLS third Party logistics integration
for finish shipment of finished goods to
distribution sites and whatnot.
So these are the big rocks that we're
going to focus on for the next three or
so months and these, like Hafeez said,
these big rocks will be
the biggest challenge that we'll face for
getting the sites ready for the S4
transformation and just a quick
understanding of the sessions and how we
plan to run them.
So essentially for we've broken down some
of these big rocks on the slide below.
Hamza, there's a question from Lisa,
sorry to interrupt.
Thank you.
Just going back to to the names on this
overall breakdown,
I can see that there needs to be a shift
in the names from the site in Helsingborg,
because I mean you have under plan,
Howayda and Cecillia Hansen.
But Cecillia Hansen is no longer working
within the company and she supported the
finance work stream.
So here we should have Max Casen.
Of course I can update that in the case
and and Max is on the call.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Thank you.
Sure, Lisa.
I believe he has the invite. So yeah,
I can give that a quick one.
Yeah, yeah. Here's here's. Yeah.
So just for clarity, just for clarity,
Yeah.
yeah.
Thanks Lisa.
Perfect. Thanks. Thanks, Lisa. Yeah.
All right.
So continuing with just the structure of
the workshops that we have,
essentially we see it as a few phases.
So for our session one,
we want to give an recap of what we know
from the Phase Zero assessment and.
As well as the oneS4 template that we
understand so far and just run a further
deep dive of anything that we haven't
covered as part of the Phase Zero phase
zero, we went into quick detail,
but we covered a lot of things.
Now we're honing in into these big rocks
and essentially trying to get extract as
much information as possible.
Needed for to understand what we have so
far as As-Is as well as the S4 template
that rolls onto our second session.
As we continue that As-Is deep dive and
then have a first cup
Of a gap analysis to understand what is
missing between the As-Is and the oneS4
template,
as well as a brainstorm of the key design
sessions for each big rock,
and then sessions 3 and 4, we
Mature these design stations that we have
right,
we take inputs from the BPO and TPO teams
as well as the sites and then come to by
the end of session four,
we should have a decision on how we can
navigate this big rock.
Which leads into Session 5 where we
report our findings to the BPOTPO leads
including the Arges and VINNIES of the
world.
Some big rocks are bigger than others.
For example,
the toll on toll manufacturing is quite a
large big rock.
So for those sessions we have some repeat
sessions.
So for example session one and Session 2
here might be doubled in that case and
we'll we'll focus a full week on either
gathering just the As-Is or.
Having that idealisation of the to-be
design.
So that is the general structure of how
we want to follow these sessions and
hopefully as we go along,
it should become, you know,
more of a drum beat rhythm in terms of
what needs to be prepared and what we're
going to look into for each session.
All right.
I think that's all I have in terms of
introduction and our project aims.
Any other questions before we go into the
deep dives and I hand it off.
All right. Perfect.
As we all know for our first session,
we are covering the finance processes,
royalty and lease management, right.
So two separate topics,
we have royalty processes and lease
processes.
We'll try cover both of them for this big
rock. However, on our detailed breakdown,
we cover them separately.
So let me hand it off and we can continue
from here.
Yes, thank you. Thank you, Hamza. Hello.
Hi, everyone.
My name is Sumedh and I am an associate
director in Innoverv Global. Yeah.
And I will be covering the royalty and
the lease management part where and I can
see some familiar faces here. For example,
Erica, I think we spoke about in the.
With for the PO accrual process with Ian.
So I'm happy to see her yet. See you here.
So I think let's start, basically. Yes.
Like Hamza said,
we are dividing this into two parts.
One is the royalty part and then we'll
move to the lease management part.
This being our first session,
what we're trying to do here is we are
trying to understand or meet you and.
Understand that. OK,
what is the information that we have,
right,
what we have understood with the existing
information that we have and maybe based
on that we can go with the clarification
process that OK? No, no,
this is not the correct understanding.
This is what it stands for and so on.
So that it will give us a base.
To go ahead with the to be process or to
talk about what can be the future in
Kenvue, right.
So let's start with the royalty process
and for this,
I think I think a very nice lady,
Anu was kind enough to share some really
nice documentation which helped us to
understand what does it existing royalty
processes.
Which we have covered in one of the other
slides. But yes,
we right now we have that information.
So let's quickly deep dive in to see what
we have as a warm up.
This is kind of a warm up slate that we
have in terms of what we have and what
are the pain points that we have
understood from the existing process,
right.
So based on the documentation that we
have right now,
what we have information is that there
are three unique royalty processes that
we have.
One is with the GSK sale that we have for
12, but there is a royalty of 12%.
Then there is another scenario where we
have the 8% part and then there is a
super royalty portion which is not
exactly royalty,
but rather than internal adjustments,
that is done to ensure that the residual
profit is transferred from one of the
entity to the another, right.
So these three scenarios is what we have
and we'll deep dive into them in the next
slide for sure.
Then the second thing is yes,
we are talking from royalty that is,
as a income.
Right.
We're talking about royalty as income
which which which can you is supposed to
receive. That's the main part,
but obviously there is some internal
process as well. For example,
I think there is a transfer that happens
between Cilag to McNeil, right.
So that becomes an intercompany
process in a way,
because in this case what happens is in
the end, yes,
royalty is still coming as part of Kenvue
as a group for sure.
But as part of internal transfer,
if we talk about this is where Cilag
plays an important role as a kind of
mediator between GSK and McNeil in terms
of this process, right, and this is?
Where I have some questions,
but we'll go into that later, yeah.
Yeah. So just just to be really clear,
it's Michelle From tax,
we're talking about JNTL CH1 not not
Cilag. That's a J&
J entity just just yeah,
so we get our facts straight. Yeah, OK.
Yeah.
Perfect. That was actually my question,
because what happened was I found one,
I got one word file where there was
reference of 2014 which was Cilag
Yeah.
everywhere.
And the presentations I think is where I
Yeah.
think we have now word ELC.
I think that's that's maybe one of the
new terminology that I saw in one of the
presentations.
But I will,
I will make sure of this and I'll make
the changes in this documentation after
this call. Yeah, for sure.
OK, great. Thanks.
Wherever there is a Cilag reference,
I will make sure it's a change to the new
OK. Perfect, great.
one. Yeah. OK. Thank you.
Thank you for identifying this part and
pointing it out. Yeah.
So yes,
I think one of the important thing that I
saw in this is yes, as part of Kenvue,
we are receiving royalty for example in
this case a third party GSK, right?
So what we have seen is that based on
based on the process flow that is there
mostly GSK is something.
GSK sends some information across in
Excel format and other formats to help.
Can you understand that? OK,
this is the sale that we have and this is
the royalty payable and so on.
And therefore after that you know we have
our entire process as to how to book the
royalty and everything.
So indirectly for the royalty portion,
we have a kind of dependency on a third
party right to give us some information
and based on that we are moving ahead and
posting the documents,
posting the royalty portion right.
Again there is I think like most of the
big entity,
we have a central processing of invoices.
For the intercompany invoice booking as
well for the third party royalty invoice
that we raised and obviously there is
accrual portion behind it as well, right?
So that is also something that was really
nicely explained in those documentation
that we have.
So that was really useful to understand
the existing Kenvue process right then in
terms of the payment terms?
I think it's quite unique for the
royalties,
different royalty scenarios that we have,
for example,
the one that we have with GSK,
the 12% part.
We have some for one of the products.
We have advanced concept why for one of
the other products we have the you know
post kind of concept where after the
quarter we raise it and so on.
So it's a variety that I completely
understand that that has to be booked in
a different way.
And obviously based on difference and
everything that true up also comes up,
which is again explained in the next
slide, right.
So we will have a very healthy discussion
on those individual royalty scenarios,
right. And I think just to summarise,
I think based on what we have right now
because of the content and everything.
Right now,
the information that we haven't please
correct me if I'm wrong,
but right now we have royalty scenarios I
think limited to Helsingborg out of some
of the sites that we have looked into,
but we'll be happy to hear if there is
some more royalty scenarios.
Especially Globe wide,
because this will really help us to
understand solutions from the global
template perspective, right?
It will really give us a vision to talk
about entire Kenvue as a whole and not
just Helsingborg over here.
So I will take just a quick pause and
happy to hear our inputs on any of the
points that I just now mentioned.
Any correction please. Please feel free.
Not corrections to this,
but there are actually other global flows
I believe outside of Helsingborg.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah,
there are a number of intercompany
royalty flows,
particularly with with the Swiss entity
Yeah.
and also with the the German entity.
But it might be worth taking it offline
OK.
because and then actually sharing with
you the royalty flows that we have.
Yeah.
In place,
maybe the royalties team can support that,
but yeah, there are a number, yeah.
Yeah,
but I think here the point they tried to
make is that relate like connected coming
from manufacturing plants.
So like maybe all the others had not
necessary connected strongly the
manufacturing plant or do we have in any
other manufacturing plant.
I think you could probably argue that
you've got Germany with OB.
Yeah, there is.
None.
So would be certainly be one that's
linked to a manufacturing plant, yeah.
Yeah, but I mean, even these points,
what we who who would be the the the
person who confirm that this is all
correct.
It would be Beatrice Rupero.
I think she was my contact when I was
trying to confirm on the flows and she
sent me a file that showed like all the
other global flows,
which I'm happy to share.
But it's her and a team that actually
does the
Postings I believe and do the full yeah,
yeah.
In big it's the.
It's the global big thing, right? OK,
Yeah.
So what you said,
we do have a process owner for this
royalty in the big organisation.
OK, we need to involve them before,
but OK,
now we can connect with them and she
would be able to confirm if these are all.
Yeah. Like to get the confirmation.
Yeah.
But also then we have a royalties team
that should be able to confirm.
OK.
You mean the one based in Manila that
post the intercompany postings? Yeah,
And.
Yeah.
Like they do all the calculations. Yeah,
yeah.
they the guys have both their names. Yeah.
Yeah. Are provided both their names. Yeah.
Yes, I think.
This might have been something Erica
might mentioned on mail.
I think we might need to contact.
See who we can also bring in.
Yep.
I included the names in when I sent you
all the documents, I can resend it again.
So it was features for for like the
royalties flow and the intercompany
Ah, perfect.
calculations.
It was Jonathan somebody so I can send
the names again.
Yeah.
Perfect. Thank you.
Alright, hand it back to you Sumedh.
Mm-hmm. Sure. Yes. Anything.
It's good to validate.
The good thing is just come back. Hamza,
I think that is on the right side.
I still have to cover the pain points.
If you go back. Yeah, but yes,
I think luckily I I use the documentation
that we have. But yes,
someone if someone can validate.
That's also nice.
Yes. On the painpoint side, again,
the documentation was beautiful.
It helped me understand the entire
accrual as well as invoicing process
right. Now,
but the main thing that I observed in
those documentation was it's kind of
manual driven. It's kind of excel driven.
Wherein the information is still coming
from outside the organisation.
For example,
in this case GSK and then we are putting
into Excel that formula then based and
then the accrual goes ahead and similarly
next for the invoicing part, right.
So the flow that is actually starting
right,
the flow or the actual process that is
starting is kind of manual.
or excel or kind of non automated process
that is in place, right?
And that's maybe one of the pain points
that I would say Kenvue would like to
resolve or move ahead with to ensure you
know it's streamlined with the other
existing process that we have for example,
there are many, many processes or maximum.
processes which are end to end managed
right from your logistics perspective
sales perspective and everything right so
similarly if something like this can be
done for royalty where things are
automatically calculated they are already
taken care of in terms of calculations
and posting I think that's maybe one of
the painpoints that I I could think of
right.
And everything that you see,
all three points are connected to the
same process.
But feel free to tell me if if there are
any more painpoints that you feel are
really blocking your overall royalty.
And I'm talking about general process,
not specific royalty scenario process,
which we'll cover in the next slide.
But in overall process that you have
right now.
Is there any other painpoint which I have
not listed down here?
I I'll be happy to look into this after
this call as well if if there is
something.
And I think it's better to go speak to
the team that do it today.
I don't think that that teams on the.
Sorry, sorry. I for me at least,
maybe there was some network connection
from my side. Can you please repeat?
I don't know if you,
I said it's better to go speak to the
team that do it today.
I don't think they're represented on this
call.
If you've got a global royalties team,
Oh.
then they're the ones feeling the pain.
OK, so I think for the next call, I think,
Hamza,
I think the list that ANU sent across,
I think we have to make sure those guys
also there so that we will have a
constructive call with them,
OK and maybe we'll,
we'll ensure that we are actually
catching all the painpoints or the
difficulties that these guys have right
now, correct.
So we'll do that. Yeah. So maybe now.
Yeah.
Perfect.
So maybe we can now move to the next
slide. Yes.
Now these are the three scenarios that we
have the as is where I've just tried to
give you a short summary.
Just trying to highlight the main points,
but everything is from our documentation
from Kenvue.
There are some things which might not be
covered here just because I wanted to
cover everything into a single slide,
but we can have a really healthy
discussion on each of these topics, right?
The first one is the most first one is
the one where we have GSK involved as a
third party, right?
And over here,
I think we have that unique process
correct and like I mentioned earlier,
you'll see Cilag over here.
Ignore that part.
I will change it to the new names for
sure after this call, right.
So this is again something.
The first thing I wanted to say is yes,
it's again a third party royalty process.
Now over here there are two entities that
are involved from Kenvue site.
The old name,
Cilag and McNeil that you say wherein the
connection is such that the patent is
actually owned by McNeil. OK.
Patent is actually owned by McNeil.
So in the end,
McNeil is supposed to receive the royalty
Right,
But what is happening is and I think
there might be some legal classification
because of which this happens,
but what usually happens is that McNeil
raises an invoice.
On Cilag, again,
ignore the wrong old name. OK,
just this is just for right now.
McNeil to Cilag and then Cilag raises to
GSK. Right the invoice.
So the invoice flow happens from McNeil
to Cilag, Cilag to GSK,
but in the end GSK pays directly to
McNeil.
OK. So in the end,
Cilag if you see it's it's it's zero over
here, that's for sure in the end,
royalty is going to McNeil and it's
coming through GSK now in this case the
entire royalty documentation,
I think dependencies on GSK side.
Where they have to give you data in a
specific format or the documentation that
has been agreed upon and after that the
entire process starts right?
So in this case indirectly and not
directly,
it's only indirectly that Kenvue has the
information coming from GSK. OK,
what is the sale?
What is the royalty part? So there is no.
Control that Kenvue has on those
information.
It's just becomes a receiver of
information.
That's why there is no logistics or any
kind of that kind of integration comes up.
It's pure finance part that comes up here
right now over here.
Also I think you have a very nice
relation with GSK where you have multiple
products where that are.
For which royalty is received from GSK.
For example,
if you see the there are two types of
payment terms here and I think in terms
of your product gum,
what happens is that it's on the advance
basis, right?
It's there on the advance basis and what
happens is that at and this is quarterly
raised, OK.
So example right now we are in the third
quarter, July, August.
September, right.
So at the beginning of July, for example,
an invoice advance invoice is raised to
GSK and based on that and what happens is
that at the end of the quarter,
whatever is the differential value that
you have right?
Because when you raise an invoice,
it's with a value, let's say X.
Right. And obviously it will not be X.
It will either be some value which is
below X or it will be above X and based
on that you will have a invoice - true-up
invoice that will be coming into play
right.
So this is what happens in one of the
product while in case of another product
and this is the only two products
information that I had right now.
Which is I think, called lozenge.
And sorry if I'm mispronouncing this now,
in this case,
what happens is it's it's fairly simple.
This is where the invoice is raised at
end of the quarter after the quarter.
So you have complete transparency in
terms of what is the sales value.
GST is already telling you, OK,
this is the sales value and this is the
royalty that is payable.
And so where there is no accrue or
everything is required, right.
But the most important thing that comes
up here is yes,
for these royalties you have accruals for
these royalties,
you have accruals which are posted
monthly, right.
And the invoices are raised quarterly.
So this becomes one of your first
scenario.
Now the second scenario is is a 8%
royalty part where again in this case
it's kind of a intercompany portion,
which I found based on the documentation
that we have in this case,
again the old name Cilagignore pays make
nearly 8% of the sale of products and.
Where obviously McNeil owns the brand or
patent right now in this case also there
is a payment term which is also little
unique.
So it's a little different from what we
saw earlier. Oh, sorry.
Before I go to scenario 2,
let's let's stick to scenario one.
Please let me know if.
If I was clear if there is something I
need to repeat or if there any questions,
anything that we can need to discuss
about the scenario one,
then only we'll move it to scenario 2 and
My first question,
maybe my first question,
is this scenario still valid?
Can anybody confirm that because the
first document that I have is from 2014
and like someone rightly pointed out it
had reference of Johnson and Johnson and
so on right?
So the first question,
is this still valid in terms of yes,
the scenario is still here. Second, yes,
the payment terms are still the same.
Third, yes,
we still have this hierarchy internal
where one intercompany one,
one of the entity raises.
Anybody can if if they can validate this
information,
that would really help us to move ahead.
Yeah, I think so. It just said my view,
I think that's the point that we don't
have here. The people who doing this.
So let's clarify what we can get out of
Right.
That's.
this course.
So I don't think it's we don't,
we should not really it is it really a
point to talk through all these steps at
Yeah.
this point with all this paper on the
core we have 25-26 people on the call but
no one is doing this process
Hmm.
So let's align and let's be clear on
accountability right by we spending our
Ah.
time with all this paper and what we try
to get out of this call.
It's good that we have tax People.
Tax people is can always keep their view
right.
So it's good to have me share feeling bad.
So let's
let's get their view that regarding
loyalty and lease,
Yeah.
what they see today as pain point,
but just let's get that view and then we
take it from it,
we take it then and then we then find the
Sure.
right contact with owning this process
today in finance have a discussion with
None.
them to go through these details we can
validate.
If this is still the case,
and then even I think also we need to do
something internally in the S4 side,
because who is owning the temp S4
template today?
Because there are some things in market
work stream on royalty.
So we need we need to connect with them
Survive.
and understand what you have an S4.
So maybe if we go step by step,
I think at this point the question for
this call,
the question is we can start with tax.
Is there anyone else who has view and
points to add what is to process?
And and Erica.
So this is Michelle from direct tax.
So in terms of these three scenarios,
they all exist today.
Yeah.
So I can tell you high level that nothing
has changed in the contracts in terms of
for the GSK royalty,
it's still a double invoicing process in
OK.
the.
JNTL Switzerland invoice and GSK and then
McNeil invoice JNTL. So it's that.
So that hasn't changed.
I don't know about the underlying payment
And.
terms or whether there's been any change
to frequency,
but the fundamental scenarios are still
still in place today.
OK. Thank you.
And anything else you would add regarding
the royalty process from tax point of
view?
Only to a point that was raised earlier,
that because of the, you know,
the very manual process there is,
you know, prone to manual to, you know,
human error and also my understanding was
last year something that came up through
the royalties team that.
Due to various tools not being available
in terms of granular level of detail on
product,
there was a problem for a period of time
in that the royalty team couldn't get the
level of detail they needed to be able to
do some of the intercompany royalty
calculations. So again it's.
Trying to find a way of automating the
processes I I guess from the GSK 12%
royalty perspective you're always going
to be relying on GSK to provide you with
data because it's their NTS on which the
royalty is based.
So only they know what their sales are
out to the trade.
We don't have that information internally,
so.
Always be that reliance on the external
party,
And.
but definitely online that with the more
automation to make it more efficient.
Thank you, Michelle.
Yeah, I think, yeah,
just coming back to the point you one of
the main things as we mentioned at the
start of the call, right.
So we what we're discussing here is what
we identified as big rocks.
Which came out of the readiness
assessment. Yeah,
the Phase Zero that was conducted for
Helsingborg and Val-de-Reuil.
Now we are trying to take it one level
deeper and and 100% point taken. You know,
we want to have that conversation with
let's say royalties.
Team that you know sits in Manila where
we'll get the detailed answers,
but to keep this session as productive as
possible, maybe you can help us direct.
You know,
what would be the best use of everybody's
time because on one side, yeah,
there is a deep dive that the team has
conducted.
To get to this level of detail,
but the idea is not to sort of pull
everybody in this call into a level of
detail where you know it,
it doesn't become relevant. Yeah,
so maybe a generic question,
if there are any specific inputs.
That anyone has at this point to help you
know,
streamline this process from an overall
S4 template perspective because I know we
have both dimensions participating in
this call.
So maybe just an open-ended question at
this point like you mentioned Erica would
be.
Definitely very useful.
So can I ask maybe a more basic question
that is towards Erica in terms of
requirements you see,
has it been brought up so far that we
need a more automated payment automated
way to manage royalties?
Obviously we have different royalty
Systems within our landscape,
Listerine is one that pops to mind.
Pretty manual, generally quite small size.
Are we looking to try and bring that into
us or if that's for the long term
ambition because SAP
doesn't do this that well.
So a lot of it would be custom in my
thinking.
So I'm just trying to get my head around
what what we hope to achieve like we can
go through the flows and and talk about
the royalties that that are owed and how
they're calculated,
how they're brought down and then
accruals that could be automated and then
even theoretically invoice or a payment
structure.
So that could be automated,
but I'm just just trying to get my head
around what we're shooting for.
Maybe the team could give us more
background why this was identified as Big
Rock.
Yeah, I mean,
this one specifically came up at at
Helsingborg. Yeah. I mean,
because if you see some of the points
that were mentioned on the as is right.
So it's it's specifically in the context
of how the the processes at Helsingborg
are structured in the context of no go go
back to that earlier slide, Hamza -
The one before. Yeah.
So when we were discussing the the
process steps at Helsingborg, right,
so one of the points related to,
I mean one of the main big rocks there
was the physical layout of the
Helsingborg site and the material
movements and so on.
But when we were prioritising these these
big rocks,
specifically for the month of August,
we asked was to focus on finance
processes and when it came to finance
processes,
this one was the the main point that was
identified because of specificities that
exist at Helsingborg.
And maybe that's a generic question.
When you read through this,
is there anything that any of you in this
call are aware?
You know that needs to be connected into
into the broader global question that
that Rishi just brought up, right?
So in in the context of the big Rock,
it was specifically related to
helsingborg based on the points.
That that Sumedh was elaborating earlier
and what I mentioned on this slide,
so this did not come up as a big rock
item for Val-de-Reuil.
So from a from a input perspective,
this is specifically about Helsingborg as
a plant.
But if it generically applies across the
board globally.
Then it's important to have that broader
conversation.
Did I clarify?
Yeah. So, so yeah,
I think it makes sense that this is a
very complicated process for Helsingborg
specifically.
So it was identified as a big rock,
which makes sense.
Correct.
But I think it's also fair to add to the
context is that OK,
when we looking royalty,
we can't just look only whether only the
has in book because there are other.
Processes and if we've looking for an S4
solution and it needs to be considered
100%.
everything and then Rishi points,
it also makes sense to say that OK,
but what? What do we do?
We really need an S4,
be it a solution for this process and I
think they also for that at this point we
don't know.
I think at this point we just need to.
To check the process and that's my
understanding is that at the end of this
Hmm.
few few discussions,
we should be able to say that yes,
actually something to build in S4 would
help in the process or maybe we don't
need anything in S4.
But I think at this point,
we don't know yet.
100% Erica. In fact,
that's exactly the the question and the
answer we are looking for. Yeah.
So the idea here is to,
OK.
because we did the Phase zero assessment
for Helsingborg, Val-de-Reuil,
Sezanne and Wuppertal. Yeah.
So specifically looking at Helsingborg,
this point came up and the the complexity
of why this came up is is as mentioned on
Yep.
this particular.
Like and as Sumedh was explaining,
but the idea of this conversation is not
Yeah.
to stay focused. Yeah,
I mean on a granular level,
the ask is to stay focused on,
on on Helsingborg,
because that's the immediate ask. But.
Of course,
we know that the the S4 template will
have to be adopted globally. Yeah.
So while we are having that conversation,
we discuss Helsingborg,
but we also discuss it in a broader
context,
how this can be adopted in a global
template.
And the image also the next question of
it,
what should be and should not be adopted
is also a question.
I mean the idea of this particular
exercise is also to ensure that we don't
enter into these roadblocks later into
the stage. So once Helsingborg kicks off,
you know,
the implementation starts and then.
You identify? Oh,
I I did not identify these issues.
And then it becomes late.
And then you have to end up,
you end up building new enhancements.
Yeah.
So we want to try and get to those kind
of answers.
Yeah. And we do have actually enhancement,
yeah.
If.
And we do have actually enhancements
regarding royalty in the pipeline.
So we need to then also connect with that.
Exactly. Yeah.
So we need to contextualise it.
Oh.
So what is already in the pipeline,
does it fulfil these requirements?
If it does, then no problem. Yeah.
Then this does not remain a problem for
Yeah.
Helsingborg. Yeah.
Is there anything specific that anyone
sees here? Which.
Doesn't you know which is not adopted in
the global template and therefore could
become a new enhancement or a new new
process design specifically for
Helsingborg
Yes, anuja.
Hi. So hi.
My name is Anuja and I work as a senior
RSP for Helsingborg.
I am not so much involved in the royalty
business as such but I'm aware of how it
is functioning.
Right now you're in Helsingborg
And since you are asking about just ideas
on maybe a way to implement this into one
S4,
what I was thinking was is we already
receive manufacturing POs from.
Cilag for example.
The product is produced and it is shipped
from Helsingborg across against an
invoice.
What could support over here is perhaps
based on the invoice quantity,
an automatic royalty PO created to Cilag
So that no manual intervention is
required from the Helsingborg perspective.
And I think that that's something similar,
but we already built.
OK.
So we started to build something back for
Canada and then I can see the enhancement
list some items for US.
So yeah,
I think we just need to then understand
what we have so far in S4 and better it
would have what has in work, yeah.
Exactly.
All right, yeah.
Yeah, perfect. So Sumedh,
I think what might make sense is,
you know,
we have a focused discussion on this
topic based on the input that anuja just
provided.
Let's have a conversation together with
Erica.
Let's look at what enhancements are
already.
In the pipeline? Yeah,
because that visibility is not there with
Mm-hmm.
us at the moment. Yeah.
So let's look at what is there and then
Yeah.
let's map it into the, let's say,
the issues that you have identified. Yeah,
Yeah, actually that's.
This was one of my questions in the next
I think that.
slide.
So we have created a list of questions,
but let's do I and this is I think I
think you were speaking from the second
scenario. For example in this case,
I think this is where my question was
specifically that is it a logistic sales
driven process because this is the kind
of thought process I also had from the.
The solution perspective right,
but I think that's fine.
What we can do is we can quickly go on
the next slide.
There are some generic questions that we
can cover.
I think key decisions we can come back to
later because I think this needs to go on
hold. So we can just quickly, yeah,
just cover some questions because we
might get some breakthrough here.
So saying we have already have some
global solutions, right?
Some of these questions are similar to
that. For example,
the first question that I had and I think
someone answered this at the beginning of
the call, which was my doubt,
are these the only three processes that
we have.
And I think if we look from global
template perspective,
I think we got the answer.
There are many more.
Right.
And that's very important to understand
because in the end,
when any solution that goes ahead right,
maybe any solution that even the global
template is working or not has been
started.
The benefit definitely is calculated
based on number of scenarios on what is
the scope of the work, right?
So example if only these three were there
in entire Kenvue,
right then obviously going for a costly
automated solution or something would not
be feasible, right? But instead of three,
if we have 13, if we have 30,
then for sure the solution and the
potential of solution changes right?
But someone already answered it.
The only thing I can request is that.
If we can have some kind of a consulted
list or a kind of maybe some more
information regarding the the royalty
scenarios that we have other than
Helsingborg,
that would really help us out, right?
Second question was also more or less
answered that are these scenarios still
valid? Yes, they are valid.
Most of the things were clear.
I think the only thing that we are not
sure about right now is the payment terms
have let me change or not.
That can also be revisited with the guys
who are actually handling right now the
royalty postings. So that's fine.
We still got the maximum information that
we wanted.
Third question is I think from global
template perspective because see the
postings are the when you are supposed to
book the royalty.
The timelines that we have,
everything is impacted by the accounting
standards that we have, right.
For example,
IFRS might say book royalty in this way,
you might have US GAP,
which might say there might be a
definition change over there, right? So.
This is where my question came up and
this is something that we can understand
once we understand how many processes are
there. For example, yes,
from Europe's side we have these many
where more or less most of the in most of
the places we have IFRS driven accounting,
right?
If there are some US based,
we have to think from that perspective
because that might impact your accrual
kind of processing and the revenue
booking for royalty, right.
So once we have that scenario,
maybe that would really give us everyone
a good perspective regarding the
different accounting standards as well as
group reporting requirement behind it.
Right then the 4th one was again kind of
answered.
Are these long term agreements are
expected to expire in foreseeable future,
so sorry, sorry this one not answered,
but I think again it's an open question
which we can get answer to later.
Because if any of these,
because usually we have a timeline, right,
the agreements are maybe 10 years,
15 years,
20 years down the line and if some of
these are supposed to mature and not be
in place, let's say one year,
two years down the line,
then there is no point in building a
solution for these kind of scenarios
because then you're,
I mean that there is no.
Benefit or cost benefit over here, right?
Then the 5th question,
which was not clear maybe from the
documentation or I missed out is
invoicing for sure is managed by the
central team right?
So for the royalties all the invoices are
managed by the central team.
The only thing I was not sure about is
the accruals for this invoice.
Is this also managed by the central team?
Or is it managed by the local team for
the respective sites?
I'm sorry the next slide please.
No,
it's still managed by the team in Manila.
It's OK,
so the accruals are managed by team in
local sites.
Sorry Manila is your is that your shared
service centre or is it the local centre?
No, no, sorry to be clear.
Local in Europe,
the manufacturing side has local finance
in make finance.
So they that scope is the side spend like
department cost,
if there is any other process discussion,
usually the teams is sitting in the two
global finance.
Teams one is in Brazil and one is in
Manila,
and this royalty has also two parts,
so there is not really a royalty team.
OK.
We don't have a royalty team.
The royalty process is today is owned by
Supply chain  Finance Peak Team Peak team.
That's the Brazil team.
And.
But we also have an intercompany
accounting team who are the one who
posted regular accrual journals like
postings between the two entities,
but they're not really process owners.
They're more like a transactional team.
Yeah.
So the process owner team is sitting in
the Brazil peak team.
OK, that that clears it up. Yeah.
Thank you.
OK.
And then I think the last question
because the last two questions are
specific scenarios.
So and those people are not here,
so we'll skip that part.
But and the 7th question that you see
here,
I think Eric already answered that that
is their solution that are built from
global template perspectives that is
being worked out. And I think we can.
And connect for that separately. Erica,
just just to see what's being potentially
built up,
happy to learn something new and hear
your thoughts as well on what's going on
over there, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. So what? Yeah. Please, please.
I can actually answer 8, so yeah,
they do a monthly accrual and then the
OK.
quarterly invoicing,
which is your month one,
month 2 will be actuals and your month
three will be - They base it on prior
Mm-hmm.
year forecast that's that's how they do
it today.
Correct.
And the true up is done at year end
basically.
Um so the the intercompany team that I'm
talking about,
they do kind of like the AP side and the
AR side of it.
OK, OK.
But but just one scenario for the GSK
part, for example, right,
let's talk about let's divide into two
Mm-hmm.
parts, the gum part, right?
So for the gum invoices sent as an
advance, right?
So it's at the beginning of the quarter
where it is sent across.
So yeah,
they do their monthly accrual based on
Uh.
the reconciliation statement that they
get from GSK,
which apparently is around mid month and
it's 1/4 in arrears.
Sorry. Come again.
Can you repeat that last sentence, please?
So it's 1/4 in arrears what we are
accruing and they normally get the
Mm-hmm.
reconciliation statement from GSK around
mid month and that's what they base their
monthly accrual on.
OK, OK, noted noted. OK,
I think that's that clears it up.
And then I think the last part is where I
just maybe this will be very generic
information because in the presentations
which were really beautiful,
I think the reference for the 8% royalty
is where we have ELC as the portion
coming is name coming up.
And for the word.
File which was little older.
We had the Cilag reference.
Yeah, they're the same. They're the same.
They are the same.
OK that clears it up and I think this is
the one that you were explaining and I
this is where I even I had the doubt that
the sales and everything I mean this
entire process is already built into
Kenvue, right.
So, for example,
ELC is where the entire manufacturing is
happening and the sales part for example.
So this information, unlike GSK,
Kenvue has complete control over it in
terms of calculations and those kind of
things.
The reason this is very important is that
the solutions will kind vary because the
first one is where you have complete.
Dependency on 3rd party to give you
information while over here it's
completely internal,
Kenvue system driven so the automations
potentially that I was even envisioning
are quite easier on the second one
because the entire information is
available internally on the Kenvue side
and so the automation will become really
easier.
But that's completely my perspective.
We have to really see.
What's going on with the solutions that
are being planned right now, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, but yes,
I think that was the main thing I wanted
to cover today for the royalty part.
We do have a couple of slides on lease if
everyone is OK, we can move there.
But before that,
if anything anyone wants to say about
royalty, that would be great.
And anything that they want to say for
the next session, OK.
In addition to the peoples that you
requested, that's really nice.
Anything else that you would like to
cover as part of royalty in the second
session so that we might we will make
sure that you know let's concentrate on
this part for the
Remainder of the week.
Move on to the release part, Sumedh
OK, OK. So I'm writing.
Let's we'll skip this one.
This is just a summary from one of the
beautiful slides that we had. Yeah.
Leasing. So in comparison to royalty,
I mean for the royalty,
we got really nice documentation in terms
of leasing.
I think we are still waiting for some
documentation.
But still, we'll try to go through there.
It might be a smaller topic to cover
today, right?
So the current information that we have
is that the forklifts are the only case
right now information and that's one of
the question also.
But what we have right now information is
forklifts which are 40 odd in count are
the only are the assets.
That are under lease management,
that's the first thing that we have.
Again,
there is a central team which takes care
of the accounting part for it for these
lease, there is an invoice that is raised.
I think it might be monthly or quarterly
based on the time frame that has been in.
Decide I did it upon and right now it's I
think there was links which was in place
for the invoicing part,
but I think it is being covered as part
of them right now.
Again for this the painpoints are
something similar to what we saw in the
royalty. It's not a automated process, OK,
it's something that is handled outside
ERP.
Then most of the leads adjustments are
done at the IFRS adjustments are done at
the group level where maybe the local
team don't have that visibility and this
is something we can check if they really
need that visibility or not right.
And yes,
because of the this excel based solutions
and everything again it's a manual work.
These are this is the only information we
have from the limited documentation that
we have for the lease management part.
But if anybody over here has any
information or any can add any point
regarding what we have or anything
additional that would be really helpful
for us to prepare for the next session.
Who manages leases today?
That's maybe my question.
I'm just trying to send why this is an
issue with with one set of forklifts.
This isn't something that's come up
before in our discussion.
So I'm trying to understand why it's been
a big Rock.
What has been highlighted as being the
issue.
Yeah. Again, Rishi,
I think it's something that came up
specifically in the context of
Helsingborg. Yeah,
I mean it's it's a specific leasing
process that happens at Helsingborg,
you know,
in terms of the the volume and and how it
sort of gets managed.
Within within that particular site it's,
it's just the the way.
If if you look at what we know you know,
so there are specific number of forklifts
there which are.
Leased and then the way that invoicing
and accounting is handled,
it's just a way it is managed today.
Manual excel based, you know,
manual journal entries.
So there was a a question that was posed.
Is there a better process to manage it in
a in a global template format so this one
is more of a question. Yeah,
so it's in in terms of the impact or the
complexity lower compared to some of the
other ones.
It basically came up as a question saying,
OK,
Yeah.
it's a painpoint in our existing process.
Is there something better that we can
look forward to?
OK.
So for now it's it's more of a question
you know is there,
is there a process already set up in,
in the S4 template you know which will
solve this problem.
Personally I believe the answer should be
yes, but just.
A question to everybody here.
Right now,
it hasn't come up in the discussions I've
had.
We haven't activated anything on the
Hmm.
contract lease management side.
We have obviously the asset management or
or fixed asset but leases.
I haven't been discussed. I have.
Yeah. And and Rishi,
just to also clarify on that point, right,
And would.
so also what we did is when we were doing
the readiness assessment,
the the Phase Zero,
we did not we we could not look at the
to-be template in in a great level of
detail.
But wherever we knew that there would be
a process to handle it,
we sort of took a a sort of a calculated
judgement that, OK,
this may not be a problem,
but since you also mentioned right that
lease management has not come up.
So maybe it turns into a potential gap
once we deep dive.
And that's the reason why it's here. Yeah,
so maybe just what?
We'll also check it from our side.
If there is a a solution which is already
envisaged here,
but if it's not then potentially this
turns into a gap, right,
which either has to be built in with
standard SAP functionality.
Or might even turn into an announcement.
So that's the deep dive investigation we
need to do here.
Yeah,
it'd be important for me to understand
what pain point we're trying to remedy.
Obviously excel based. I get it.
That's not great,
but where's the pain and that?
So we have so we can keep clear what?
Yeah, and.
SAP is capable of doing because if you
take an Excel spreadsheet and you say
look each month I have to make payment
for $10,
000 or whatever the currency being used
here, Swedish kroner,
Hmm.
then that's that isn't very difficult to
set up.
You don't have to set up the whole
condition contract.
And track it like you know the granular
level.
You could set up some form of repeat
payment or anything like that to keep
keep on top of it.
Yeah, it's a very yeah, sorry.
So.
So yeah, that was out for me.
Is just trying to ensure that when we
talk about pain point is what pain that
we're trying to relieve ourselves of.
Yeah, I'll,
I'll try and explain and maybe if there's
somebody who can explain it from a site
perspective,
I know we have some limited participation
in this call today conscious of that.
But one of the main pinpoints that came
up at Helsingborg repeatedly, Rishi is.
You know, firstly they are on.
I don't want to digress this discussion.
Yeah.
So but just to give an overall context at
the moment,
they use a very old system called MoveX
as an ERP. Yeah, it's it's, I mean,
if I can say that,
you know it's painfully old,
you know it's one of the oldest systems
Yeah, familiar with it.
I've come across in.
Yeah. So that's movex.
And then what to address the the system,
what they have done is they have created
a number of Excel spreadsheets,
some 300 plus to be honest,
which are consolidated into a framework
called Data Mart.
And those excel spreadsheets are then
used to solve a number of their
operational topics. You know,
on one side it could be transaction
management and on the other side,
it's also reporting.
So what happened was when we were going
through this.
We went through a lot of those Excel
spreadsheets, you know,
to look at where they are and a number of
them would get solved directly with
standard SAP functionality. You know,
material movements, inventory management,
material numbering.
Batch management, et cetera, et cetera.
You know some related to quality
management and so on. This one,
we were not sure and that's why we
captured it as one of the the potential
big rocks just to check that you know it
doesn't appear as as a.
As a gap later in the process,
So what we'll also do if unless if
somebody can already answer it here in
terms of the volume and the complexity of
the effort, we'll we'll verify that.
If it turns out it's a low volume,
low effort activity which can continue to
be managed in Excel.
And we don't on one side we it has not
come up in any other site and therefore
we don't have a standard SAP solution in
the template.
And looking at the volume and the
complexity,
we don't even think it should be built
continuing with an Excel solution is.
Is good enough? Maybe that's our answer.
Yeah. So right now,
the idea was just to put it out out here
and and to arrive at that kind of a
conclusion.
So that then we capture it as a design
decision that it's specific to
Helsingborg. It's not a global problem.
It's not so high volume, high complexity.
It can continue to be managed in Excel,
so be it.
Yeah,
but we just need to get to that answer in
a factual,
databased way that that's all the
intention was here.
Did I clarify?
Or any follow on question.
OK.
Yeah, thanks for this background.
I think at least for me,
it helped a lot like it's really
clarifies how we get to this point.
But my view is that OK,
at this point then now we need to find
who are the people who doing this process
and who are actually the ones who has
Hmm.
this pain point, right.
And we need to talk with them and that's
actually not an easy task.
in today's Kenvue work with all the
global regional teams? But like,
that's the next step, right?
We need to discuss with that specific
Yeah, we'll we'll take that.
I think that's one of the main.
that those specific people.
Yeah,
I think that's one of the main takeaways
from this call. Yeah. I mean on one side,
we want to ensure we have all the right
OK.
participants in these calls. So,
so as we make this absolutely productive,
Yeah.
Yep.
yeah.
So we definitely need the right site
participation. Yeah, yeah.
We'll we'll work on ensuring that.
OK.
And then also when we are discussing a
specific topic like we discussed.
discussed on the royalty,
maybe we'll also have to identify if
there are specific central teams,
you know,
like we we just discussed earlier in in
this call. Yeah,
we need to ensure that they are there so
that they can then rubber stamp this,
you know, OK,
this is actually my pinpoint.
Can you solve this please?
Yeah, or this is not OK.
If you tell me I have to manage it in
Excel. Fine for me.
I continue the way I'm doing it today.
Yeah,
and that allows us to get to those key
design decisions quicker and then we are
able to close these points. Yeah.
But I think personally I think just based
on this discussion,
we already made good progress. You know,
we have to now clarify those.
Those open questions quickly and then
then we get to those answers that we want.
Hey,
is there anyone on the on the call who
can help clarify some of the doubts that
were raised Anuja since you mentioned
earlier on the royalty, you know,
just sorry I don't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's plant specific, yeah.
OK. No, sorry. Didn't want no.
Didn't want to put you on the spot,
but just wanted to ask if there's anyone
else who can who can answer it similar
Yeah.
like how you did for the royalty?
Yeah. If not,
we'll we'll go back to the site and and
try and get this clarification.
I think the person who has highlighted
the the leasing process to us during the
phase series was Christian and Cecillia.
I think as we knew,
Cecillia has left and Christian,
I believe he's out of office for today.
So I'll try get them specifically.
Yeah.
Oh,
at least Christian on a one-on-one on
this try. See his understanding.
And if there's any wider teams involved.
Yeah.
Yeah, Hamza,
let's also capture that as as a learning
for the next session. Yeah,
so that you know,
if some of the key stakeholders,
if they're not,
then we we act as mediators, you know,
I mean that's not ideal all the time.
Yeah.
So we we could literally get to a
conclusion here, you know.
What is the volume?
What is the complexity? Yeah. OK.
Cool.
That enough?
So I think let let's park these questions
right now. Summit, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Pleasure.
OK.
Is there anything else we wanted to cover?
I'm just conscious of the time. I mean,
we have 24 people on the call.
If we can give back the time,
let's do that.
Yeah, yeah.
Anything else we wanted to cover?
Hafeez is anything to add from your side.
No, nothing from my side at least.
No, I think we're good.
We got most of the questions addressed.
Some are still pending to be you know,
from the global teams that we need to get.
Like Erica pointed out,
once we have the connects from them,
we'll reestablish another call with the
global teams to understand exactly what
they're doing today.
And then see how we can map it out into
SAP
And as Rishi mentioned as well,
we didn't looked into contract and lease
management,
maybe that's another area that we can
explore and see how we can enable that
capability within SAP.
Yeah.
Previous I think if if we can conclude
then we'll share minutes as well as the
attendance.
Yeah.
And Erica if you can share the names of
the global team participants who can join
can take that as an action for the next
call on Friday to see if those folks can
be invited.
And then we can close out.
I've sent that for royalties already have
fees. I've sent the name for royalties.
Yeah. Good.
All right. Perfect.
I think that's an hour on the dots.
I think we'll give 25 minutes back to
everyone.
We'll get in contact with the royalty
teams.
I think we will have a focus session and
then hopefully for next week,
we can bring them along into the wider
forum here.
Great. Thank you. Thank you. Thanks, Eva.
Thank you. Bye.
OK. Thank you. Thank you. Bye, bye.
Thanks everyone. Bye. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Bye, bye.
Thank you. Bye bye bye.